http://www.breeches.com/pages/privacy-policy

Find out the Breeches.com Privacy Policy
Breeches.com understands the importance of ensuring the privacy of the users of our website and the information they provide. This privacy statement is intended to provide all users with confidence when visiting Breeches.com through a thorough outline of the information collected and how it is used to better serve our customers and enhance their relationship with our company.
Information Collection and Use Breeches.com collects information from visitors of the website and subscribers of our emails and other forms of communication. Domain and email information of each visitor to our website is not collected by our Web server. We do, however, collect email addresses of visitors who choose to supply us with their email address by signing up to receive communication from us or opt to correspond with us using email.
Additionally, we do compile various information on what pages consumers visit, user on-site behavior, and any other information volunteered by the consumer. This information is collected and reviewed internally for the purpose of improving the Breeches.com website’s functionality including, but not limited to, content, usability, layout, and customer contact for marketing and promotional purposes. Breeches.com holds this information as confidential and will not sell or give away any of your personal information to a third party.
Ordering When ordering from Breeches.com, customers must provide complete and accurate contact information, including name, mailing address, phone number, and email address. This information is helpful in ensuring all orders are processed as accurately and as timely as possible, as well as enables our company to provide a more personalized experience when consumers make a purchase.
Permission In order to provide our customers with up-to-date information regarding their account or orders, we may communicate with the customer using email, phone, or regular mail from time to time. Additionally, we also offer customers the option to receive information about Breeches.com, our products, and special promotions. There is no obligation, however, to receive this information from us and customers can choose to opt out.
If at any time you receive information from us that you do not wish to receive in the future, please contact us by emailing customerservice@breeches.com or submitting the form on our Contact Us page and indicating this preference. Every effort will be made to cease all unwanted communication as quickly as possible; however, please understand that it is possible that you will continue to receive communication until your request can be processed.
If you decided at any time you would like to resume receiving communication from Breeches.com, please contact us using the contact us page or by sending an email to customerservice@breeches.com.
Security Every reasonable precaution is taken to protect our customers’ personal information. All sensitive information is encrypted and transmitted securely via SSL encryption. In addition, we restrict access to all sensitive customer information. Information is only accessed by employees as necessary to complete specific job functions. Lastly, all personally identifiable information is stored in a secure server environment.
Link to Outside Websites On occasion, Breeches.com may provide links to outside websites that visitors and customers may find useful. In these cases, Breeches.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these outside websites. Please refer to the privacy and/or policy page of these websites for information on how your information may be used.
Notifications and Changes In the event that there is a modification to our privacy statement, Breeches.com will post changes on this page to ensure that all customers can familiarize themselves with the information we collect, how it is stored, and how it is utilized. It is advisable that customers periodically review this page to become familiar with any changes that may occur.
ReviewsAs images submitted to supplement written reviews are able to be utilized by Breeches.com for advertisements and marketing purposes.
